mdjunction.com 2011-10-25

# Privacy Policy

MDJunction is an open community of patients who share, in public, their experiences and knowledge.  We respect your right to privacy.  This Privacy Statement is to inform you about our privacy practices, it applies to all web sites owned and operated by MDJunction.com. 

**General Guidelines for privacy**  
When browsing any website on the internet (MDJunction.com included) – it is strongly recommended that you do not reveal your personal home address, personal phone numbers or any other personal information that is not public knowledge. 

**Personal Information \- Members**  
Registered members must provide their personal email address (as well as account username and password that we store for your convenience).  
Your email address is required for administrative purposes and to retrieve your password and username in case those are lost. As described in our FAQs you may opt not to receive administrative and other notification emails. We also collect non-personal information such as your IP address and URLs (web pages) you arrived from and visit on while on our site. 

Information you fill out via your account page (Member Profile Information) is optional and can be viewed by other visitors to MDJunction.com. Any information you post (including but not limited to photos, hugs, forum posts, diary entries, doctor reviews, ribbon descriptions and articles) on public sections of the site can be viewed by anyone. You should think carefully before disclosing any Personal Information in any Public Area. 

**We strongly believe in your right to privacy. We will NOT sell, distribute or otherwise abuse your personal information. ** 

**Children under age 13**  
We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not attempt to register or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address.   
If you find or believe that we might have information from or about a child under 13 years, please contact us ASAP. 

**Children between 13 and 18**  
Almost all the members at MDJunction.com are over 18 and thus oriented to interacting with others who are in the same age group.  
We do not allow children under 13 to register to MDJunction but also recommend and insist that minors over the age of 13 years ask their parents for permission before registering to MDJunction, sharing any personal information or talking to anyone over the internet.  
If you are between the age of 13 and 18 and not sure if MDJunction is the right place for you, please talk to your parents or contact us. In any case please use caution.  
We recommend that minors over the age of 13 years ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from the site you are visiting and stored on your computer's hard drive.  
Cookies are very common and are being used by most websites. Cookies do not harm your computer nor can they access information stored on your computer.  
The primary purpose of cookies is to maintain your customized settings on the site. The site login process ("Remember my password", for example) and member functionality requires that your browser accept cookies. 

**Links and Other sites**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to review the privacy statements of each and every Web site that you visit through MDJunction.com. 

**Information Collected by Third Parties  
**We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. 

You can always change your information (profile information, username, screen name, email preferences, etc) via your member account page. Check out the FAQs (link at the bottom of every page) on how to do it. 

To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information,you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**Security**  
MDJunction.com implements methods of securing its user information databases from unauthorized access or alteration. 

**Amendments to the privacy policy**  
This policy may be amended from time to time and in our sole discretion, upon posting notice on the Web site. Please periodically visit this page to review the current privacy policy. 

**Accreditation**  
MDJunction complies with the principles of the HON Code of Conduct established by the Health on the Net Foundation. To verify our compliance, click on the HON logo. 

**Please feel free to[contact us](http://www.mdjunction.com/contact) with any questions. **

Privacy page was updated on February 2010.   
  
**Important** : Articles published in MDJunction are written by MDJunction's community members and not by medical professionals (unless stated directly). They are not medical articles/content and are not a replacement for medical diagnosis. If the article does not contain direct reference to the source of the data, please treat it as personal opinion of the writer.
